Finding Aid for Edwin Franko Goldman Autograph Collection
Bentley Historical Library
Edwin Franko Goldman Autograph Collection
circa 1770-1954
1850s-1940s
Bentley Historical Library
Goldman, Edwin Franko, 1878-1956
9560 Aa 2
1 linear foot (in 2 boxes)
Edwin Franko Goldman (1878-1956) was an American composer and conductor for military bands. Collection, assembled by Goldman, of autographs, letters, photographs, and musical scores of many musical celebrities from his lifetime and before.
The collection was donated by the University of Michigan Band in 1995. Donor no. 7024
The collection is open for research.
Edwin Franko Goldman (1878-1956) was an American composer and conductor for military bands. As an avocation, he was also a collector of autographs, letters, photographs, and musical scores of many musical celebrities from his lifetime and before. In May 1954 he donated his collection to University of Michigan band director William Revelli for use by the band. The "Edwin Franko Goldman Room" in Harris Hall at the University of Michigan was dedicated to display the collection.
The Edwin Franko Goldman Autograph Collection consists of two series: Background Materials and Autographed Photographs and Manuscripts. The collection contains autographs, letters, photographs, and musical scores of such notable musical celebrities as Antonin Dvorák, George Gershwin, Franz Liszt, Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart, John Philip Sousa, Johann Strauss, and Igor Stravinsky.
Composers.; Conductors.; Musicians.; Photographs.; Bantock, Granville, Sir, 1868-1946.; Benedict, Julius, Sir, 1804-1885.; Bennett, William Sterndale, Sir, 1816-1875.; Bruch, Max, 1838-1920.; Brüll, Ignaz, 1846-1907.; Bruneau, Alfred, 1857-1934.; Chabrier, Emmanuel, 1841-1894.; Chambers, William Paris, 1854-1913.; Chaminade, Cecile, 1857-1944.; Costa, Michael Andrew Agnus, Sir, 1808-1884.; De Koven, Reginald, 1859-1920.; Delibes, Léo, 1836-1891.; Delius, Frederick, 1862-1934.; Dvorák, Antonin, 1841-1904.; Franz, Robert, 1815-1892.; Gade, Niels W. (Niels Wilhelm), 1817-1890.; German, Edward, Sir, 1862-1936.; Gershwin, George, 1898-1937.; Gilmore, P. S. (Patrick Sarsfield), 1829-1892.; Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich, 1865-1936.; Goldman, Edwin Franko, 1878-1956.; Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893.; Henselt, Adolf von, 1814-1889.; Herbert, Victor, 1859-1924.; Hérold, Ferdinand, 1791-1833.; Holst, Gustav, 1874-1934.; Joachim, Joseph, 1831-1907.; Lecocq, Charles, 1832-1918.; Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886.; Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847.; Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864.; Miller, George.; Millöcker, Carl, 1842-1899.; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791.; O'Neill, Charles, 1882-1964.; Plunkett Green, Harry.; Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943.; Raff, Joachim, 1822-1882.; Randegger, Alberto, 1832-1911.; Reinecke, Carl, 1824-1910.; Respighi, Ottorino, 1879-1936.; Rubinstein, Anton, 1829-1894.; Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951.; Sibelius, Jean, 1865-1957.; Sousa, John Philip, 1854-1932.; Strauss, Johann, 1804-1849.; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971.; Sullivan, Arthur, Sir, 1842-1900.; Thomas, Ambroise, 1811-1896.; Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916.; Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893.; Volkmann, Robert, 1815-1883.; Waldteufel, Emil, 1837-1915.; Vaughan Williams, Ralph, 1872-1958.; Goldman, Edwin Franko, 1878-1956.; University of Michigan. Symphony Band.
- Background materials
  Background Materials, consists of a single scrapbook of photographs, newspaper clippings and other materials related to the dedication of the Goldman Room in 1954.
  - Scrapbook, May 18, 1954 (Box 1)
    (consisting of news clippings, photographs and memorabilia documenting Goldman's appearance as guest conductor of the U of M Symphony Band, his stay in Ann Arbor and the dedication of Goldman Room)
- Autographed photographs and manuscripts
  Autographed Photographs and Manuscripts, consists of autographs, letters, photographs and musical scores of musical celebrities. Materials have been arranged alphabetically. Oversized materials are located in Box 2 of the collection.
  - Abt, Franz. German composer (Box 1)
    - Letter and photograph, 1869 (Box 1)
  - Adam, Jean Louis. French pianist and composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Albeniz, Issac. Spanish pianist and composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Alvary, Max. Operatic tenor
    - Autographed photo, 1895 (Box 1)
  - American Band Masters Association
    - Photographs, 1929; 1935 (Box 2)
  - Arbuckle, Matthew
    - Letter and portrait postcard, 1880 (Box 1)
  - Arditi, Luigi. Italian composer and conductor
    - Letter and photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Bach, J.S. German composer and organist
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Bachman, Harold
    - Autographed photo, undated (Box 1)
  - Balfe, Michael William. Irish operatic composer and singer
    - Portrait postcard and autographed Note, 1844 (Box 1)
  - Bantock, Granville. English composer and operatic conductor
    - Letter, musical notation and photograph, 1908 (Box 1)
  - Barrère Georges. French flutist
    - Photograph (Box 1)
  - Beach, Amy Marcy. American pianist and composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Bell Over the Shoulder Horns, Musical group
    - Autographed photo and autographed note, 1932 (Box 1)
  - Bellini, Vincenzo. Italian opera composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Benedict, Sir Julius. Pianist, composer and conductor
    - Letter, 1870 (Box 1)
  - Bennett, William Sterndale. English pianist and composer
    - Autographed note with musical notation and portrait, 1856 (Box 1)
  - Berlioz, Louis Hector. French composer
    - Portrait postcards, undated (Box 1)
  - Bilik, Jerry H. American composer and band arranger
    - Photograph (Box 1)
  - Bishop, Henry. English composer
    - Letter and portrait, 1852 (Box 1)
  - Bizet, Georges. French composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Borodine, Aleksandr. Russian composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Bottesini, Giovanni. Italian composer and musician
    - Photograph, Circa, 1870 (Box 1)
  - Brahms, Johannes. German composer and pianist
    - Photograph, Circa, 1880 (Box 1)
  - Bruch, Max. German composer and conductor
    - Autograph with musical notation and photograph, 1904 (Box 1)
  - Bruckner, Anton. Austrian composer and organist
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Brüll, Ignaz. Austrian pianist and composer
    - Letter and photograph, 1879 (Box 1)
  - Bruneau, Alfred. French composer and music critic
    - Letter and photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Buck, Dudley. American composer and organist
    - Letter and photograph, 1888 (Box 1)
  - Busch, Carl
    - Autographed portrait postcard with musical notation, 1920 (Box 1)
  - Busoni, Ferruccio. Italian composer and pianist
    - Autographed photo, 1915 (Box 1)
  - Cadman, Charles Wakefield. American composer and music critic
    - Autographed photo, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Carpenter, John Alden. American composer
    - Autographed photo, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Caruso, Enrico. Italian tenor
    - Autographed photo, 1903 (Box 1)
  - Chabrier, Emmanuel. French composer
    - Letter and portrait, 1882 (Box 1)
  - Chambers, William Paris
    - Letter and photograph, 1906 (Box 1)
  - Chaminade, Cecile. French composer and pianist
    - Letter and photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Charpentier, Gustave. French composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Chausson, Ernest. French composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Chopin, Fredric. Composer and pianist
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Clarke, Herbert L. American musician
    - Autographed photographs, 1938; undated (Box 1)
  - Clarke, Herbert L. and Frank Holton. musicians
    - Autographed photo, undated (Box 1)
  - Clarke, Herbert L, Walter Smith, Del Staiger and Frank Simon. Musicians
    - Autographed photo, undated (Box 1)
  - Clement, Fredric. French tenor
    - Portrait, undated (Box 1)
  - Copland, Aaron. American composer
    - Autographed photo, 1948 (Box 1)
  - Costa, Michael. Italian composer and conductor
    - Autographed musical notation and photograph, 1876 (Box 1)
  - David, Felicien. French composer
    - Letter and photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Debussy, Claude. French composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - DeKoven, Reginald. American composer
    - Letter and photograph, 1907 (Box 1)
  - Delibes, Léo. French composer
    - Letter 1836 and portrait postcards, undated (Box 1)
  - Delius, Frederick. English composer
    - Letter and photograph, 1924 (Box 1)
  - Dietz. Musician
    - Photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - D'Indy, Vincent. French composer
    - Letter, 1917 (Box 1)
  - Dubois, Théodore. French composer
    - Autographed note (Box 1)
  - Dvorák, Antonín. Czech composer
    - Letter with musical notation and photograph, 1884 (Box 1)
  - Elgar, Edward. English composer
    - Letter and photograph, 1925 (Box 1)
  - Fall, Leo. Austrian composer
    - Autographed photograph with musical notation, 1912 (Box 2)
  - Falla, Manuel de. Spanish composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Fauré, Gabriel. French composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Fijiian Band. Marching band
    - Photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Fillmore, Henry
    - Autographed photo, undated (Box 1)
  - Flotow, Baron Friedrich von. German composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Foote, Arthur. American composer
    - Letter, undated (Box 1)
  - Franko, Nahan. Band master
    - Autographed photographs, 1889 (Box 1)
  - Franz, Robert. German composer
    - Letter and photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Gade, Niels Wilhelm. Danish composer and conductor
    - Portrait and letter, 1883 (Box 1)
  - Gadski, Johanne. Singer
    - Autographed portrait (Box 1)
  - German, Edward. English composer and conductor
    - Autographed letter and photograph, 1902 (Box 1)
  - Gershwin, George. American composer
    - Letter and photograph, 1927 (Box 1)
  - Giese, Fritz
    - Autographed photo, 1883 (Box 1)
  - Gilmore, P.S. (Patrick Sarsfield). American band master
    - Letter 1892 and photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich. Russian composer
    - Autographed photo with musical notation, 1929 (Box 1)
  - Gluck, Christoph. German composer
    - Portrait postcard, Circa, 1770 (Box 1)
  - Godard, Benjamin. French composer
    - Autographed photo, undated (Box 1)
  - Goldman, Edwin Franko. American composer and conductor
    - Photographs, 1949; 1954; undated (Box 2)
  - Goldmark, Rubin
    - Letter and autographed photo, 1915 (Box 1)
  - Gomes, Carlos. Brazilian composer
    - Letter and stamp, 1890 (Box 1)
  - Gounod, Charles. French composer
    - Letter, photograph and portrait postcards, undated (Box 2)
  - Gretchaninoff, Aleksandr. Russian composer
    - Portrait postcards, undated (Box 1)
  - Grieg, Edward. Norwegian composer
    - Autograph and portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Hahn, Reynaldo. Venezuelan composer
    - Letter and photograph, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Hanson, Howard. American composer
    - Autographed photo, undated (Box 1)
  - Heifetz, Jascha. Russian-American violinist
    - Autographed photo, 1920 (Box 1)
  - Hempel, Frieda. Operatic soprano
    - Autographed photo, 1926 (Box 1)
  - Henselt, Adolf. German composer and pianist
    - Letter and photograph, 1882 (Box 1)
  - Herbert, Victor. Irish-American composer and conductor
    - Letters and photograph, 1918; 1923 (Box 1)
  - Hérold, Ferdinand. French composer
    - Letter and portrait, 1830 (Box 1)
  - Hoeth, Theodor. Cornetist
    - Autograph and photograph, 1901 (Box 1)
  - Hofmann, Josef. Polish pianist
    - Autographed photograph, 1898 (Box 1)
  - Holmes, Augusta. French composer
    - Letter and photograph, 1902 (Box 1)
  - Holst, Gustav. English composer
    - Letter and photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Honnegger, Aurthur. French composer
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Huber, Hans. Swiss composer
    - Letter and portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Humperdinck, Englebert. German composer
    - Autographed portrait (Box 1)
  - Innes, F.W. Band master
    - Autographed photo, 1902 (Box 1)
  - Joachim, Joseph. Hugarian violinist
    - Autograph, envelope and photograph, 1887 (Box 1)
  - Kalliwoda, Johann Wenzel. Czech composer and violinist
    - Autographed musical notation and portrait, undated (Box 1)
  - Kienzl, Wilhelm. Austrian composer and writer on music
    - Autographed musical notation, 1899 (Box 1)
  - Kocian. Bohemian violinist
    - Autographed photo, 1902 (Box 1)
  - Koschat, Thomas
    - Autograph and photograph, 1905 (Box 1)
  - Krehbiel, Henry Edward. American music critic
    - Photograph, 1910 (Box 1)
  - Kreisler, Fritz. American violinist
    - Autographed photo, 1912 (Box 1)
  - Kretschmer, Edmund. German composer and organist
    - Letter and photograph, 1878 (Box 1)
  - Kreutzer, Conradin. German composer and pianist
    - Autographed letter, 1823 (Box 1)
  - Lalo, Edouard, French composer
    - Portrait postcard and autographed title page, undated (Box 1)
  - Leboff, Henry
    - Autographed photo, 1877 (Box 1)
  - Lecocq, Charles. French composer
    - Letter and portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Lehar, Franz. Composer
    - Autographed musical notation, 1912 (Box 1)
  - Leidzen, Erik
    - Autographed photo, 1945 (Box 1)
  - Leoncavallo, Ruggiero. Italian operatic composer
    - Autographed note and clipping (Box 1)
  - Levy, Jules. American cornetist
    - Letter 1902 and photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Liberati, A. American band master and cornetist
    - Letter and photographs, 1888; 1920 (Box 1)
  - Lichtenberg, L
    - Photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Liszt, Franz. Hungarian pianist and composer
    - Autographed letter, undated (Box 1)
  - Litchfield, Barbara
    - Photograph, 1946 (Box 1)
  - MacDowell, Edward Alexander. American composer and pianist
    - Portrait (Box 1)
  - Mackenzie-Rogan, J. Band master
    - Autographed photo, undated (Box 1)
  - Manunely, L
    - Autographed photo with musical notation, 1894 (Box 2)
  - Marching band related cartoons
    - Cartoons, 1939; undated (Box 2)
  - Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix. German composer, conductor and pianist
    - Letter and portrait postcard, 1845 (Box 1)
  - Meyerbeer, Giacomo. German composer
    - Envelope, letter, autographed portrait postcards and photograph, 1839; undated (Box 1)
  - Milhand, Darius. French composer
    - Portrait (Box 1)
  - Miller, George. English band master
    - Letter and photograph, 1932 (Box 1)
  - Millöcker, Carl. Austrian composer
    - Letter and photograph, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Moor, William
    - Autographed musical notation and photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Moscheles, Ignaz. Bohemian composer, pianist and teacher
    - Postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Mottl, Felix. Austrian composer and conductor
    - Autographed portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus. Austrian composer
    - Musical notation and portrait, circa 1770 (Box 1)
  - Mozkowski, Moritz (?) Composer and pianist
    - Letter (Box 1)
  - Muck, Karl. German conductor
    - Autographed photo, undated (Box 1)
  - Nevin, Ethelbert. American composer
    - Autograph (Box 1)
  - New York Philharmonic with Arturo Toscanini, Conductor
    - Photograph, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Nicolai, Otto. German composer and conductor
    - Letter and portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Nikisch, Arthur. Hungarian conductor, pianist and violinist.
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Nordica, Lillian. American operatic soprano
    - Autographed photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Offenbach, Jacques. French composer and musician
    - Portrait postcards, undated (Box 1)
  - O'Neill, Charles. Canadian band master
    - Letter and portrait, 1929 (Box 1)
  - Paderewski, I.J. Polish pianist and statesman
    - Autograph and photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Patti, Adelina. Soprano singer
    - Autographed photo, 1890 (Box 1)
  - Philippine Army Band
    - Autographed photo, 1948 (Box 1)
  - Pierné, Gabriel. French composer and conductor
    - Autographed note and portrait postcard, 1905 (Box 1)
  - Plançon, Pol. French operatic basso profundo
    - Autographed photograph, 1903 (Box 1)
  - Plunkett Greene, Harry
    - Autographed musical notation and photograph, 1890 (Box 1)
  - Pontiac High School Band
    - Autographed photograph, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Prokofieff, Sergei. Russian composer
    - Autographed title page and portrait postcard, 1937 (Box 1)
  - Pryor, Alexander. Band master
    - Autographed photo, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Rachmaninoff, Sergei. Russian composer, conductor and pianist
    - Letter and autographed photo, 1937 (Box 2)
  - Raff, Joachim. German composer
    - Letters 1871, 1872 and portrait postcards, undated (Box 1)
  - Randegger, Alberto. English composer and conductor
    - Autographed musical notation and photographs, 1903 (Box 1)
  - Reger, Max. German composer
    - Autographed portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Reinecke, Carl Heinrich. German composer, conductor and pianist
    - Musical notation 1824 and photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Remenyi, Edward. Hungarian violinist
    - Autographed photo, 1879 (Box 1)
  - Respighi, Ottorino. Italian composer
    - Letter and photograph, 1932 (Box 1)
  - Richter, Hans. Hungarian conductor
    - Autographed musical notation and photograph, 1894 (Box 1)
  - Ries, Franz. Composer, music publisher and violinist
    - Autographed photographs, 1894; 1928 (Box 1)
  - Rogers, Walter B
    - Autographed photo with musical notation, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Root, George Frederick. American composer
    - Autographed musical notation and portrait, undated (Box 1)
  - Roussel, Albert. French composer
    - Postcard and autographed title page, undated (Box 1)
  - Rubinstein, Anton. Russian pianist and composer
    - Letter and photograph, 1865 (Box 1)
  - Rusiheweyh, E
    - Autograph and photograph, 1893 (Box 1)
  - Safranck, V. F
    - Letter and autographed photo, 1933 (Box 1)
  - St. Jacome
    - Photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Saint-Saëns, Camille. French composer, organist and pianist
    - Portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Santelmann, W.S. American band master
    - Letter and photograph, 1906 (Box 1)
  - Sarasate, Pablo. Spanish composer and violinist
    - Photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Scarlatti, Alessandro. Italian composer
    - Portrait, undated (Box 1)
  - Scharwenka, Phillip. German composer
    - Autographed musical notation, 1890 (Box 1)
  - Scharwenka, Xavier. German composer and pianist
    - Autographed musical notation, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Schoenberg, Arnold. Austrian composer
    - Autographed note and photograph, 1934 (Box 1)
  - Schuch, Ernst von
    - Autographed photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Schumann-Heink, Ernestine. Operatic singer
    - Autographed photo, 1903 (Box 1)
  - Seidl, Anton. Hungarian conductor and musician
    - Autographed musical notation and autographed photographs, 1894., 1888 (Box 2)
  - Sembrich, Marcella
    - Photograph, 1903 (Box 1)
  - Servant, F.A
    - Autographed photo, 1902 (Box 1)
  - Shelly, Harry Rowe. American composer and organist
    - Autographed musical notation and photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Sibelius, Jean. Finnish composer
    - Letter and autographed photo, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Simon, Frank. Cornetist
    - Autographed photograph, 1937 (Box 1)
  - Sinding, Christian
    - Letter, 1910 (Box 1)
  - Sindsley, Mark
    - Autographed photograph, 1937 (Box 1)
  - Smith, Walter M. Cornetist
    - Autographed photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Sousa, John Philip. American band master and composer
    - Autographs, letters, musical manuscript, photos, and program notes, 1882-1932 (Box 1)
      (also in oversized box 2)
  - Spalding, Albert. American violinist
    - Autographed photograph, 1916 (Box 1)
  - Spohr, Louis. German composer and violinist
    - Photograph, 1836 (Box 1)
  - Straus, Oskar. Austrian composer
    - Autographed musical notation, 1912 (Box 1)
  - Strauss, Johann. Austrian composer and conductor
    - Letter and portrait, 1838 (Box 1)
  - Strauss, Johann (Jr.)
    - Autographed note, 1891 (Box 1)
  - Strauss, Richard. German composer and conductor
    - Autographed portrait postcard, 1922 (Box 1)
  - Stravinsky, Igor. Russian composer
    - Letter and portrait postcard, 1937 (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Sir Arthur Seymour. English composer, choir master, and organist
    - Letter and photograph, 1881 (Box 1)
  - Suppe, Franz von. Austrian composer
    - Photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Taylor, Deems. American composer and music critic
    - Autographed Photo, undated (Box 1)
  - Thomas, Ambroise. French composer
    - Letter and photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Thomas, Theodore. Orchestra conductor
    - Autographed photo, undated (Box 1)
  - Tosti, Paolo. Italian-Born English composer
    - Letter, 1904 (Box 1)
  - Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich. Russian composer
    - Letter and photograph, 1884 (Box 1)
  - University and College Band Conductors
    - Photograph, 1941 (Box 2)
  - Vaughan Williams, Ralph. English Composer
    - Letter and autographed photo, undated (Box 1)
  - Verdi, Giuseppe. Italian composer
    - Portrait and portarait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Vohst, Carl. Cornet teacher of John Phillip Sousa
    - Autographed photo, 1894 (Box 1)
  - Volkmann, Robert. German composer
    - Letter and photograph, 1867 (Box 1)
  - Wagner, Richard. German composer
    - Caricature 1863 and photographs, undated (Box 1)
      (see also oversize in box 2)
  - Waldteufel, Emile. French composer
    - Autographed musical notation, 1905 (Box 1)
  - Weber, John C. Band master
    - Autographed photo, 1936 (Box 1)
  - Weber, Karl. German composer, conductor and pianist
    - Portrait, undated (Box 1)
  - Weinberger, Javomiv
    - Autographed portrait, 1939 (Box 1)
  - Weingartner, Felix. Composer, conductor and writer on music
    - Autographed photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Widor, Charles Marie. French composer and organist
    - Letter and portrait postcard, undated (Box 1)
  - Wieniawski, Henry. Polish composer and violinist
    - Photograph, circa 1835-1880 (Box 1)
  - Wilhelmj, August. German violinist and composer
    - Portrait, 1890 (Box 1)
  - Ysaÿe, Eugène. Belgian violinist
    - Photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Unidentified photographs and manuscripts, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Accession of additions, 2005; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Oversized photographs and manuscripts (Box 2)